ILLIASSE MOUNJIM

Software Developer

Denver, CO

GitHub.com/IliasMounjim

(303) 974-8500

in LinkedIn.com/in/illiasse-mounjim

illiasse.mounjim@gmail.com <a> Iliasmounjim.github.io/Portfolio



Versatile US Army veteran with a Computer Science degree and 2+ years of experience, eager to prove my value and talent in the evolving tech industry. Problem solver and excellent communicator with strong work ethic, a unique blend of skills, and exceptional adaptability. Seeking an entry-level position to advance and expand my skill set through mentorship and challenging projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web App Developer

Freelance

Mar 2021 - Present

- Denver, CO
- Designed and developed sophisticated and fully customized business websites for multiple organizations, aligning it with company's branding and business objectives, resulting in enhanced online visibility and user engagement.
- Collaborated closely on the creation and seamless integration of customized features and functionalities using PHP, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap and plugins to architect robust and responsive web solutions, ensuring seamless performance and user satisfaction.

Manager - Dispatcher and Driver

Boulder Limo

🗰 Apr 2019 - Present

- Denver, Co
- Proficiently managed operations, combining dispatch and driving responsibilities, showcasing multitasking skills and a commitment to operational excellence.
- · Facilitated seamless communication between drivers, customers, and higher management, optimizing service coordination and contributing to operational efficiency.

Dispatcher and Customer Service Rep.

H&M Towing and Roadside Assistance

May 2020 - Present

- Receiving emergency and non-emergency calls, dispatching appropriate crew members and drivers, monitoring and tracking driver status and service delivery status.
- Communicating and coordinating between customer, insurance representatives, crew members, and management in the most effective manner.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's in Computer Science

University of Colorado Denver

and Aug 2019 - Dec 2022

Denver, CO

Relevant courses: Algorithms, OOP, Data Structures, RDBMS, Computer Networks, Web APIs, IoT, and Software Engineering design

Advanced Individual Training

U.S Army Armor School

Sep 2015 – Feb 2016

Fort Benning, GA Relevant courses:

Electronic, mechanical, and hydraulic systems, Schematics, NBC(Nuclear, Biological, Chemical) defense, Teamwork and Leadership

TECH SKILLS

Python, C++, Java



 Developed multi-threaded applications as well as advanced concurrent and distributed applications using modern software engineering techniques, pattern design approaches, and reusable components.

MySQL, Oracle, MongoDB

 Experience with in-depth design of database systems including query

M1A2 Abrams Tank Maintainer

US Army

Apr 2015 - Apr 2019

- US, Europe
- Expertise in maintaining and repairing intricate M1A2
 Abrams tank systems, including the Honeywell turbine
 engine, transmission, electrical, suspension, steering,
 hydraulic, auxiliary power, fire suppression, gas systems,
 and NBC protection system.
- Exercised meticulous asset management protocols for a significant segment of US Army equipment exceeding a valuation of \$50 million during a challenging international deployment, maintaining impeccable accountability and bolstering mission accomplishment.
- Mastered the operation of advanced machinery and equipment, resulting in my appointment as the designated equipment operator due to superior proficiency showcasing a natural ability for swift learning and seamless adaptation to cutting-edge technologies.
- Played a key role in creating an efficient management system of resources, including tools, equipment, and spare parts, ensuring their availability and optimal utilization in support of technical objectives.

AWARDS & HONORS

x2 U.S. Army Commendation Medal

- Nov/2017 For meritorious service and performance of duty at the NATO Joint Multinational Readiness Center in HOHENFELS, Germany
- Aug/2016 For willingness to go above and beyond duties assigned at the NATO Joint Multinational Training in Zagan, Poland

x3 U.S. Army Achievement Medal

- **Feb/2016** For Honors Graduate performance in the U.S. Army Advance Individual Training in Fort Benning, GA
- Aug/2016 For Peak performance in the U.S. Army National Training Center in Fort Irwin CA
- Jan/2019 For the outstanding performance of duty at the U.S. Army Fort Carson Armor Gunnery.

U.S. Army Good Conduct Medal

• 04/2018 For continuous honorable and faithful service

HOBBIES

Football (soccer), skiing, reading, working out, traveling, music and swimming.

processing and optimization, transaction processing, triggers, concurrency control, recovery, and distributed databases.

PHP, HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap

 Proficient in creating visually appealing and responsive web interfaces to ensure seamless user experiences and consistent design across various devices.

Other Technologies,

JavaScript, React, GO, Racket, Julia, GIT, Google Cloud Platform, PostgreSQL, NoSQL Heroku.

SOFT SKILLS

Collaborative and Creative Problem Solving, Communication, Teamwork, Customer Service and Satisfaction, Leadership, Management, Attention to details, Fluency in multiple languages, Adaptability, and Flexibility,

CERTIFICATION

- **Current** Google Cybersecurity by Coursera
- **Apr/2019** Automotive Repair training Transition and Career Skills Program
- **Dec/2018** U.S. Army BLC (Basic Leadership Course) training for Non-Commissioned Officers
- Apr/2016 Heavy-duty wheeled and track vehicles driving licenses

<u>REFRENCES</u>

Boulder Limo - General Manager

Ed Adil- (303)-332-3992

H&M Towing and Roadside Assistance – Manager

Moe Heresh - (720)-499-6834

U.S. Army - Master Sergeant

MSG Juan Pereira – (832)-776-7336